<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>(Emilio) Blacksmith Blog</title><link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/</link><description>Recent content on (Emilio) Blacksmith Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Emilio Blacksmith</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:10:46 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Returning to Blogging</title><link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/posts/first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:10:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/posts/first/</guid><description>Hello World Hello everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s good to be back, and welcome to my personal dev / personal / blog site. The purpose of this website is to have a place to place every single idea, every single new knowledge and thing in general that I think might be really good to share to everyone.
I used to have another blog site I used to have another website, for my personal blog, it was developed using HUGO, just like this website (a static site generator), the issue with that last website it was mostly in the way it was developed, it was very poorly coded, and overall was like my little monster (A.</description></item><item><title>About Emilio Blacksmith</title><link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/about-hugo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/about-hugo/</guid><description>Howdy 🤠, I&amp;rsquo;m Emilio (Blacksmith) Herrera, a Software Engineer from México, I have a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in &amp;ldquo;Interactive Design&amp;rdquo; (UX/UI). And self taught experience transitioning towards Software Development.
I started my Development Journey, in 2017, focused on game development in general, I started using Unity with C# programming language, and ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing the transition towards software development focused on full stack web development, the transition started in 2021, I started doing more and more websites and web applications.</description></item></channel></rss>