<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on (Emilio) Blacksmith Blog</title><link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on (Emilio) Blacksmith Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Emilio Blacksmith</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:10:46 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Returning to Blogging</title><link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/posts/first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:10:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/TheBlacksmithBlog/posts/first/</guid><description>Hello World Hello everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s good to be back, and welcome to my personal dev / personal / blog site. The purpose of this website is to have a place to place every single idea, every single new knowledge and thing in general that I think might be really good to share to everyone.
I used to have another blog site I used to have another website, for my personal blog, it was developed using HUGO, just like this website (a static site generator), the issue with that last website it was mostly in the way it was developed, it was very poorly coded, and overall was like my little monster (A.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="hello-world">Hello World</h2>
<p>Hello everyone, it&rsquo;s good to be back, and welcome to my personal dev / personal / blog site. The purpose of this website is to have a place to place every single idea, every single new knowledge and thing in general that I think might be really good to share to everyone.</p>
<h3 id="i-used-to-have-another-blog-site">I used to have another blog site</h3>
<p>I used to have another website, for my personal blog, it was developed using HUGO, just like this website (a static site generator), the issue with that last website it was mostly in the way it was developed, it was very poorly coded, and overall was like my little monster (A.K.A. I was like Frank-N-Furter, making my little &ldquo;Rocky Horror&rdquo;).</p>
<p>So I decided to remake it, using the same tools, another theme, a more focused theme, focused on, the important thing, the words and ideas.</p>
<p>Hopefully this will not be that boring to read, but, it is important to me, just to have a direct conversation with you (the reader). As a UI/UX graduate, my focus is in your experience, and making sure that the idea comes across directly to you.</p>
<h3 id="what-to-expect">What to expect?</h3>
<p>Just a little side note, what you shall expect in this blogs, will be a combination of everything, from talking about my last experience with life, how I&rsquo;m improving my FOMO, how I&rsquo;m trying to be a better developer, things and facts that might be useful to be a better developer, and probably a shit ton of random thoughts and Ideas that I want to give to the world.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m a big fan of the idea of the idea of predestination, the idea that maybe by doing something, it might lead you towards another path, being open to new experiences, and people. So by doing this I&rsquo;m allowing myself to express myself better, maybe one day someone might read this and be like: &ldquo;Damn, this dude is weird, I like him&rdquo;.</p>
<p>So overall I feel like this is a Win Win.</p>
<h2 id="goodbye-space-cowboy">Goodbye Space Cowboy</h2>
<p>THAT&rsquo;S IT, thank you so much for reading this random person&rsquo;s personal blog post. It has been a pleasure, and I&rsquo;m excited for what&rsquo;s coming, stay tuned&hellip;</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>